- So we're here doing a video,
which is kind of interesting
'cause we're doing a video
making a video of making a video.
You know, there's lots of things
going on at the same time.
It's not like the normal
kind of promo clip.
("Easy Lover" by Phil
Collins and Philip Bailey)
♪ Easy lover ♪
♪ She'll get a hold on you believe it ♪
♪ Like no other ♪
♪ Before you know it
you'll be on your knees ♪
♪ She's an easy lover ♪
♪ She'll take your heart
but you won't feel it ♪
♪ She's like no other ♪
♪ And I'm just trying to make you see ♪
♪ She's the kind of girl you dream of ♪
♪ Dream of keeping hold of ♪
♪ You'd better forget it ♪
♪ You'll never get it ♪
♪ She will play around and leave you ♪
♪ Leave you and deceive you ♪
♪ Better forget it ♪
♪ Oh you'll regret it ♪
♪ No you'll never change
her, so leave it, leave it ♪
♪ Get out quick 'cause
seeing is believing ♪
♪ It's the only way ♪
♪ You'll ever know ♪
♪ She's an easy lover ♪
♪ She'll get a hold on you believe it ♪
♪ Like no other ♪
♪ Before you know it
you'll be on your knees ♪
♪ She's an easy lover ♪
♪ She'll take your heart
but you won't feel it ♪
♪ She's like no other ♪
♪ And I'm just trying to make you see ♪
♪ You're the one that wants to hold her ♪
♪ Hold her and control her ♪
♪ You'd better forget it ♪
♪ You'll never get it ♪
♪ For she'll say there's no other ♪
♪ Till she finds another ♪
♪ Better forget it ♪
♪ Oh you'll regret it ♪
♪ And don't try to change
her, just leave it, leave it ♪
♪ You're not the only one,
cause seeing is believing ♪
♪ It's the only way ♪
♪ You'll ever know, oh ♪
(Phillip laughing)
♪ No, don't try to change
her, just leave it, leave it ♪
♪ You're not the only one,
ooh seeing is believing ♪
♪ It's the only way ♪
♪ You'll ever know, oh ♪
♪ She's an easy lover,
she's a easy lover ♪
♪ She'll get a hold on you believe it ♪
♪ She's like no other ♪
♪ Before you know it
you'll be on your knees ♪
♪ She's an easy lover ♪
♪ She'll take your heart
but you won't feel it ♪
♪ She's like no other ♪
♪ And I'm just trying to make you see ♪
♪ Trying to make you see ♪
♪ She's an easy lover ♪
♪ She'll get a hold on you
believe it, get a hold on you ♪
♪ She's like no other ♪
♪ Before you know it
you'll be on your knees ♪
♪ You'll be down on your knees ♪
♪ She's an easy lover ♪
♪ She'll take your heart
but you won't feel it ♪
♪ You won't feel it ♪
♪ She's like no other ♪
♪ And I'm just trying to make you see ♪
♪ Trying to make you see ♪